Are your legs open?
足開いてる?
Chan
ちゃん
and?
と?
Properly
ちゃん と
Are your legs open?
足 開いてる?
Is it coming out?
出てきちゃってる?
Come to the front?
手前来て?
Get soaked?
びっしょびしょになる?
what happened?
どうしたの?
No?
ダメ?
What is it?
なんだよ?
It's soaking wet...
びっしょびしょになってるね...
That's amazing...
すごいよ...
Are you going to serve something like this?
こんなの出しちゃうの?
Did something like this come out?
こんなの出ちゃったの?
Try making this.
ここを製作してごらん
Wow, you look happy.
すごい、嬉しそうだね
Do you like dick?
チンチン好きなの?
Doesn't it feel slimy?
なんかヌルヌルになってない?
It's a very broad touch.
すごい広い触り方するね
Did you touch it?
それを触ったの?
Where did you learn to touch like that?
そんな触り方、どこで覚えたの?
You can do it without using your hands like that.
そんな手を使わずできるんだ
...
Roll it under
下 で転がして
Ru...
る...
That's amazing...
すごいね...
It feels so good...
すごい気持ちいい...
That's amazing...
すごいですね...
It's good...
うまいね...
Feels good
気持ちいい
...
You're really good at it...
すごい 上手だね...
Just a little...I'm going to sleep...
ちょっとさ...寝るから...
cute
かわいい
...
You're good at it...
上 手だね...
It's so rolling
すっげーコロコロしてるね
...
amazing...
すごい...
Wow...the atmosphere has come out...
やば...すっげー大気出てきた...
It's a bed bed...
ベッドベッドだね...
why
なんで
Can you do that?
そんな できるの?
Do you study like that?
そういう勉強もするの?
What is an idol?
アイドルって
...
It comes out amazing
すごい 出てくる
...
Below Is there more?
下 もっとある?
Is it okay?
いい の?
Just put it in like this...
このまま入れて...
Which one feels better?
どっちの方が気持ちいい?
This way?
こっち?
amazing...
すごい...
feelings
気 持
Is it okay?
ち いい?
With your feet...
足でさ...
Can you hold it?
かかえてごらん?
Open your legs properly...
足ちゃんと開いて...
Open it up...
し っかり開いて...
It's so open
すっごい開いてるね
...
It's making great sound
すごい 音出てるね
...
Wow, my butt came out...
すごい お尻出てきたよ...
Something came out...my butt...
なんか出てきたよ...お尻部分...
Awesome...
すっごい...
amazing
すごい
...
Would you like to float by yourself?
自 分で浮いてごらん?
can't do it
できない
...
Like this, back and forth
こう やって前後にさ
...
I don't understand...
わか んない...
Why don't you move it so it feels good?
気持ちいいように動かしてごらん?
It feels the best...
一番気持ちいい...
I don't know...
わかんない...
Oh no...
やだ...
It feels really good though...
めちゃくちゃ気持ちいいんだけど...
It's done
できてる
Yo...
よ...
Very tight
すっごいきつい
...
amazing...
すごい...
Get behind me...
手後ろについてさ...
Can you open your legs?
足開いてごらん?
Both legs...
両足...
Can you open your legs?
足開いてごらん?
Actually, why don't you just put your foot in slowly?
実はゆっくり足入れしてごらん?
spread your legs
足開けて
...
Can you see where it's in?
入 ってるところ見える?
You can see it, right?
見えるでしょ?
Where it's in...
入ってるところ...
Isn't it embarrassing?
恥ずかしいでしょ?
Ah, it feels good
あ〜気持ちいい
...
legs spread
足 開いて
...
Have you slept yet?
もう 寝たの?
Awesome
すっごい
...
I can't stand it anymore...
もう 我慢できない...
Can I take it out now?
もうさ...出していい?
Can I put it inside?
中に出していい?
Is it okay?
いいの?
Is it no good?
ダメなの?
I can't stand it...
我慢できない...
I'll take it out... okay?
出すよ...いい?
Mud came out...
泥って出てきた...
amazing...
すごい...
Now...
今さ...
dance?
踊る?
That's enough...
十分で...
Did it come out all messed up?
めちゃめちゃ出たの?
Do you understand?
わかる?
Open your legs a little...
ちょっと足開いて...
It's amazing right now...
今すっごい...
This... isn't just my liquid, right?
これは...俺だけの液体じゃないよね?
hey
ね
picture?
え?
Let's do it again...
また しようね...